<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Conference on Pennydropper - Lightbulb moments in Data Science</title>
    <link>/tags/conference/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Conference on Pennydropper - Lightbulb moments in Data Science</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en_us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/conference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Melbourne Data Science Conference 2018</title>
      <link>/2018/09/30/melbourne-data-science-conference-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/09/30/melbourne-data-science-conference-2018/</guid>
      <description>The 2018 Melbourne Data Science Conference (MeDaScIn Conference) featured data science career advice from 6 presenters. The conference, held on Wednesday 26 September 2018, was staged at the NAB Arena in Docklands.
Overall, the conference presented some good common sense career advice though there was little “new” material.
This blog post shows notes taken during the presentations.
Scott Wilson: How to Engage Executives and the Boardroom Scott Wilson, the founder of Wilson AI, presented on “How to Engage Executives and the Boardroom”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>useR! 2018 Conference Reflections</title>
      <link>/2018/07/17/user-2018-conference-reflections/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/07/17/user-2018-conference-reflections/</guid>
      <description>useR! 2018 Confernce: Brisbane 10-13 July 2018. I had 2 main objectives in attending this year’s global “useR! 2018 Conference”, the global R users’ conference in Brisbane:
1. To develop R programming skills;
2. To reinvigorate my passion for building data science solutions using R.
R “hex” map of Australia, with each hexagon representing an R package
 Develop R Programming Skills
I sat in on presentations about some cool and useful packages in many of the sessions, but all that they did was point me in the right direction and then leave me complete the journey on my own.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>