<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Forecasting on Pennydropper - Lightbulb moments in Data Science</title>
    <link>/tags/forecasting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Forecasting on Pennydropper - Lightbulb moments in Data Science</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en_us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/forecasting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>useR! 2018 Conference Reflections</title>
      <link>/2018/07/17/user-2018-conference-reflections/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/07/17/user-2018-conference-reflections/</guid>
      <description>useR! 2018 Confernce: Brisbane 10-13 July 2018. I had 2 main objectives in attending this year’s global “useR! 2018 Conference”, the global R users’ conference in Brisbane:
1. To develop R programming skills;
2. To reinvigorate my passion for building data science solutions using R.
R “hex” map of Australia, with each hexagon representing an R package
 Develop R Programming Skills
I sat in on presentations about some cool and useful packages in many of the sessions, but all that they did was point me in the right direction and then leave me complete the journey on my own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AFL Tipping Mark 1</title>
      <link>/2018/03/12/afl-tipping-mark-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/03/12/afl-tipping-mark-1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Just like many other high-profile sports with an extended round-robin series, complementary competions have spun off the AFL season for amateurs followers. These tipping competions are particularly prevalent in work environments and social groups and are quite distinct from betting competions. The most frequent format, by far, for tipping competions features tippers submitting a tip for each game of the round, with the scores tallied at the end of the round.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>